<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aidan Meacham</title>
    <link>https://aidanmeacham.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aidan Meacham</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 16:36:23 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aidanmeacham.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FA2020</title>
      <link>https://aidanmeacham.com/fa2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 16:36:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aidanmeacham.com/fa2020/</guid>
      <description>This page contains materials related to our submission to Forum Acusticum in December 2020.
Auralization of a Hybrid Sound Field using an Energy-Stress Tensor Based Model Updated slides (.pdf, 5.64 MB)
Demonstration video on YouTube (unlisted)
FVTD repository on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MATLAB utility: sendToRemote</title>
      <link>https://aidanmeacham.com/post/matlab-utility-sendtoremote/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 13:25:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aidanmeacham.com/post/matlab-utility-sendtoremote/</guid>
      <description>sendToRemote: A MATLAB utility for running code on a remote server In the course of iterating on simulation code that was painful enough on my local machine to merit running on a more powerful server, I found myself copying code back and forth, shelling in and out, and feeling like I was losing a lot of time to &amp;ldquo;bookkeeping&amp;rdquo; rather than actually working on my code.
So, I spent a lot of time writing a utility so I could handle the situation directly in MATLAB rather than switching back and forth between the local IDE and terminal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial report: ∂’Alembert learns git</title>
      <link>https://aidanmeacham.com/post/tutorial-report-dalembert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 12:05:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aidanmeacham.com/post/tutorial-report-dalembert/</guid>
      <description>Quick update! It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I&amp;rsquo;ve updated the site (beyond cursory CV updates), so this and the next few posts will be a quick dump of some of the projects I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on.
Tutorial: Version Control &amp;amp; Git on January 31, 2020 Back at the end of January (almost 3 months ago!!), I gave a tutorial for interested doctorants / post-docs / faculty at the Institut ∂’Alembert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://aidanmeacham.com/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 18:27:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aidanmeacham.com/publications/</guid>
      <description>Google Scholar.
Lower bound on frequency validity of energy-stress tensor based diffuse sound field model. Aidan Meacham, Roland Badeau, Jean-Dominique Polack. Presented at and published in the proceedings of ICA (Aachen, 2019).
A lower bound on the frequency validity limit is established for an energetic wave equation derived from the energy-stress tensor, examined in the one-dimensional case [Dujourdy et al, Acta Acustica united with Acustica 103:480-491, 2017]. In practice, the bound is encountered when determining the absorption and diffusion coefficients by iteratively approaching the temporal and spatial decay of measured data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://aidanmeacham.com/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 18:27:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aidanmeacham.com/cv/</guid>
      <description>Aidan Meacham PhD, Acoustics, Sorbonne Université - Paris, France
Acoustic Engineer - San Francisco, California, USA
https://aidanmeacham.com/cv/
https://www.linkedin.com/in/aidanmeacham/
Education Sorbonne Université, 2018 - 2021 PhD, Specialization in Acoustics, Institut Jean le Rond ∂&amp;rsquo;Alembert, thesis defended December 9, 2021
Toward Three-Dimensional Computation of the Acoustic Energy-Stress Tensor. Thesis directors Jean-Dominique Polack (Institut ∂&amp;rsquo;Alembert) and Roland Badeau (LTCI, Télécom Paris, Université Paris-Saclay).
Theoretical Acoustics. Studied statistical late reverberation through an energetic wave equation in energy density and sound intensity (similar to diffusion equation approaches) to efficiently model sound fields in large spaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ways to Include Images in Hugo</title>
      <link>https://aidanmeacham.com/post/including-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 19:36:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aidanmeacham.com/post/including-images/</guid>
      <description>What started out as an attempt to put together a travelogue turned into a rabbit hole about how best to store and reference images. There is some valuable discussion about where the topic may end up (who knows, maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll learn Go and take a crack at it myself), but also details the methods that are currently being used to various effect. One other topic I wanted to explore is the figure shortcode, which supports a little more information than a simple markdown image, and is more flexible for use with a theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://aidanmeacham.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 21:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aidanmeacham.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Stanford The Laptop Accordion - A new musical instrument. Download the paper here.
Alexsounder - Sound visualization sculpture.
Digital Waveguide Network Reverberation in Non-Convex Rectilinear Spaces. Download the paper here.
Low-cost open-source ribbon microphone. Some documentation here, laser cutter files and instructions forthcoming.
Remote data collection and uploading via cell networks. Originally used as a tide sensor; leveraged as a complex LFO for musical effects. See some of the source code here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://aidanmeacham.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 21:27:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aidanmeacham.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there!
My name is Aidan, and I&amp;rsquo;m a PhD student studying acoustics at Sorbonne Université in Paris. The subject of my doctoral studies is extending a fast late reverberation model based on the conservation of the wave-stress tensor to three dimensions.
I spend a lot of my time in San Francisco, CA, where I worked as an acoustic engineer at Knowles Electronics / Intelligent Audio. In that capacity, I performed virtual data creation and microphone array optimization for IoT devices, as well as audio DSP research and development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding Email Forwarding... Eventually</title>
      <link>https://aidanmeacham.com/post/add-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 21:07:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aidanmeacham.com/post/add-email/</guid>
      <description>A reminder: When it comes to DNS, patience is a virtue. I&amp;rsquo;ve set up email forwarding through mailgun.com, or at least expect that will be the case when DNS resolves. Once that happens, feel free to say hi via the address at the bottom of the page.
EDIT: This works now. Say hi if you like!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test post; please ignore</title>
      <link>https://aidanmeacham.com/post/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 16:42:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aidanmeacham.com/post/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Keep watching this space! As I work on migrating, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to find my projects and publications here.
Thanks to gsempe for the tutorial!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>